<resources>
    <string name="app_name">practical 14_4</string>
    <string name="demo_text">
        Android, operating system for cellular telephones and tablet computers.
        Android began in 2003 as a project of the American technology company Android Inc.
        To develop an operating system for digital cameras. In 2004 the project changed to become an operating system for smartphones.
        Android Inc., was bought by the American search engine company Google Inc., in 2005.
        At Google, the Android team decided to base their project on Linux, an open source operating system for personal computers.
        On November 5, 2007, Google announced the founding of the Open Handset Alliance, a consortium of dozens of technology and mobile telephone companies, including Intel Corporation, Motorola, Inc.,
        NVIDIA Corporation, Texas Instruments Incorporated, LG Electronics, Inc., Samsung Electronics, Sprint Nextel Corporation, and T-Mobile (Deutsche Telekom).
        The consortium was created in order to develop and promote Android as a free open source operating system with support for third-party applications.
        Android-based devices use wireless networks in order to take full advantage of features such as one-touch Google searches, Google Docs (e.g., word editors, spreadsheets),
        and Google Earth (satellite mapping software).
        Android Studio is the official Android development tool or, to be more precise, an integrated development environment (IDE) built on IntelliJ IDEA.
        It was first announced in May 2003 at the Google I/O — the annual developer conference held in Mountain View.
        Android Studio supports various programming languages like Java, Kotlin, C++, or Go to provide vast opportunities for building applications for every type of Android device.
        The software includes code editing, debugging, and performance tools. Developers can also take advantage of such features as a visual layout editor, APK analyzer, fast emulator,
        or real-time profilers. Android Studio was designed to help you create high-quality apps, streamlining the entire development process.
        The Android operating system was first developed by Android, Inc., a software company located in Silicon Valley before Google acquired it in 2005. Investors and electronics industry
        analysts have questioned Google’s true intentions for entering the mobile market space since that acquisition. But in any case, soon thereafter, Google announced the impending rollout
        of its first commercially available Android-powered device in 2007, although that product actually hit the marketplace in 2008.
        Since then, software and application developers have been able to use Android technology to develop mobile apps, which are sold through app stores, such as Google Play.
        And because it is developed as a Google product, Android users are given the opportunity to link their mobile devices to other Google products, such as cloud storage, email platforms,
        and video services.
        The Android source code is released in an open-source format to help advance open standards across mobile devices. However, despite being released as “open,”
        Android is still packaged with proprietary software when sold on handset devices.
        The Android operating system is most frequently used on different mobile platforms around the world. It is occupied approximately 75% of shares in the worldwide market by the end of 2020.
        A company like Open Handset Alliance has developed the first Android that depends on the customized version of the Linux kernel as well as other open-source software.
        At the initial stage of 2005, Google sponsored the project and it obtained the entire company. In September 2008, the first Android device was released in the market to dominate
        the mobile industries due to several features like user friendly, the support of the community is huge, customization, manufacturing of android devices in large companies. Consequently,
        the market examines the demand to develop Android-supported devices with smart developers. So, the Android operating system became a complete set of operating systems for different devices
        like wearables, mobiles, notebooks, smart TVs, tablets, set-top boxes, etc.
    </string>
</resources>